<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>

<document>
  <head>
    <title>About</title>
    <created>2012-04-17</created>
    <modified>2011-04-17</modified>
  </head>
  <body>
    <div id="document-body">
      <h3>Authority Title List</h3>
      <p>
        The authority title list draws on a spine catalogue of
        Prokofiev compositions created for this resource. Combining
        earlier Prokofiev catalogues with current scholarship, this
        resource allows users to search for a work in the language
        (Russian, French, German, or English) of its original
        manuscript or published title. A uniform title for each work
        binds variant titles together under one entry.
      </p>
      <img src="/public/img/spine.png" alt="PCDA works authorities index with related archival content" />

      <h3>Catalogue Entry</h3>
      <p>
        Standard catalogue information, such as genre, instrumentation
        and date of composition, are linked to works that share these
        components. User may search by each field – genre,
        instrumentation, date, among others – to collate works that
        share features. 'Offshoot' works, such as arrangements,
        adaptations and works rooted in the same material, receive
        independent entries while representing their relation to other
        compositions in Prokofiev's output. For a sample catalogue
        entry click <a href="{$URI_ROOT}/works/58">here</a>.
      </p>
      <img src="/public/img/pcda-er.png" alt="PCDA entity relationship diagram" />

      <h3>Manuscripts</h3>
      <p>
        Prokofiev's rigorous methods of composition often allow an
        archaeological context for works to emerge. The list of
        manuscripts under each entry represents, usually incompletely,
        different phases of conception as the work progressed from
        abstract sketch to complete autograph score. Manuscript types
        include: sketch of 'germ' themes (melodic and rhythmic);
        sketches identifiably linked to a work; draft short score;
        elaborated draft short score; draft score with scoring
        indicated; autograph score; complete score created by
        copyist. Letters linked to each entry provided vital testimony
        to the genesis of compositions.
      </p>
      <img src="/public/img/compositional-method.png" alt="Prokofiev's compositional methods" />

      <h3>Digitized Sources</h3>
      <p>
        The Prokofiev Catalogue and Digital Archive digitally captures
        crucial sketches, catalogues, scores and letters relating to
        Prokofiev's compositions that are housed in the Prokofiev
        Archive. These sources are linked to the relevant work
        catalogue entries. Attached to each digitized item are
        transcriptions, translations and information about the item's
        provenance; this metadata sheds light on how digitized primary
        sources relate to a work.
      </p>
    </div>
  </body>
</document>
